Give me some time
To blow the man down
(Leonard:)Hello?
[IN UNISON]
Hello.
Come quickly, lay aft
To the break of the poop
To me way, hey
Blow the man down
Or I'll help you along
With the toe of my boot
PENNY & SHELDON:
Give me some time to blow the man down
(Leonard:)What's going on?
(Sheldon:)I assume you're referring
to the sea shanty.
(Sheldon:)It's a rhythmic work song
to increase productivity.
Yeah. It's crazy, but it works.
(Penny:)Look, we made this Penny Blossom
in under three minutes.
(Leonard:)Terrific, but that kind of raises
more questions than it answers.
(Sheldon:)Penny's making hair accessories.
(Sheldon:)I'm helping her optimize
her manufacturing process.
(Sheldon:)All right, break's over.
[SINGING] Pay attention to orders
Now you one and all
(Howard:)- What are you using as a bonding agent?
- Hot glue.
(Howard:)You're kidding. Any of the cyanoacrylates
would do a better job.
- Won't work. The flower's porous.
- What if we infused the bottom layer...
...with silicone RTV
to provide a better mounting surface?
(Sheldon:)Intriguing.